autoraptor.com 2019-07-16

# Privacy Policy • AutoRaptor

### AutoRaptor CRM Privacy Policy – Updated as of 5-14-2018

AutoRaptor is thankful for the opportunity to help our customer reach their goals. We are committed to ensuring that our customers’ privacy is respected and protected. 

This privacy policy sets out how AutoRaptor uses and protects any information that you give AutoRaptor when you visit our website and web application. 

Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information (PII) in accordance with our website. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context.   

### Data Collection

AutoRaptor collects limited non-personally identifying information your browser makes available whenever you visit a website. This information includes: your Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your query.

We may collect the following information from you when you fill out a form on our site in order to follow up on your inquiry regarding AutoRaptor CRM as well as to set up a new account and process billing.

  * Name
  * Email Address
  * Phone Number
  * Company Name
  * Type of Dealership
  * Other relevant information to the dealership looking to use our service

### Data Use

We use the information we collect from you when you send an inquiry, sign up for our service, sign up for our newsletter, respond to marketing communication, visit the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

  * To carry out any mutually agreed upon contract obligations.
  * To process billing transactions for our service.
  * To follow up after requests for information (email, text, phone inquiries, or support requests)
  * To notify you about changes to our service.
  * To send periodic communications regarding our service.
  * To help diagnose any problems with our server and administer our website.
  * To improve our products and services.

### IP Tracking and Cookies

We use IP Address tracking technology to identify businesses visiting our site and the pages that are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic in order to develop and improve our website for business visitors.

We do use cookies in order to track your visit to our website. These cookies track location, browsers, time on page, and page visits. This technology does not identify you personally; it simply enables us to compile statistics about our visitors and their use of the website. We use this anonymous data to improve the content and functionality of the website to better understand our customers and visitors, and to improve the service we offer.

We also use cookies for our web service in order to provide our customers with the best experience, such as authentication cookies for account login.

### Third-party Disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to process such information only on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

We may also release information when it’s release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect AutoRaptor’s or others’ rights, property or safety.

In the event of a transfer of ownership of AutoRaptor CRM, we will provide notice before any personally identifying information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

### Security

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks. We implement a variety of security measures when a user submits their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

We restrict access to your personally identifying information to employees who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### Data Accuracy and Communication Preferences

To correct or update personal information, please send an e-mail to [support@autoraptor.com](mailto:support@autoraptor.com) and request the change. In addition if you wish you change your communication preferences, AutoRaptor provides you the opportunity to opt-in, opt-out or change preferences via a link in the footer of most email and text messages you receive. 

If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for marketing or customer support purposes, you may change your mind at any time by emailing us at [support@autoraptor.com](mailto:support@autoraptor.com) or calling 1-888-421-6533.

### Changes to this Policy

Please note this Privacy Policy will change from time to time. We will post those changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will also provide a more prominent notice. Each version will be noted at the top of the page.

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.

AutoRaptor CRM  
144 Westminster St. Suite 200  
Providence, Rhode Island 02903  
United States

support@autoraptor.com
